

Aleksandar Damjanovski

Nationality: Macedonian/citizen of the Republic of North Macedonia

Date of birth: 20/06/1978 **Gender:** Male **\ Phone number:** (+389) 75373069

■ Email address: <u>djacikabt@gmail.com</u>

• Home: Abdul Kerim Pasha 9, 7000 Bitola (North Macedonia)

ABOUT ME

I work as a dispatcher with Dry Van for almost 1 year and have my personal brokers who help me with providing good rates. I work with Echo, CH Robinson, Molo. I am able to work in any time provided. I am an enthusiastic, self - motivated, reliable, responsible and hard working person. I am a mature team worker and adaptable to all challenging situations. I am able to work well in a team but also on my own as I like to set myself goals which I will achieve. I am able to work under pressure and adhere to strict deadlines. I am friendly person, honest and punctual. I am well organized and always plan ahead to make sure I manage my time well. I am quick to learn and willing to adapt to any job.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Graphic tehnician Flexo machine operator

KIRO DANDARO [05/09/1999 - 12/12/2011]

City: Bitola

Country: North Macedonia

Technical and operations director

KALMAK - FELIKS FLEKSO [10/10/2011 - 01/12/2018]

City: Strumica

Country: North Macedonia

Graphic tehnician Flexo machine operator

ENIGMA PLAST - AKVABIT [10/01/2019 - 01/02/2022]

City: Bitola

Country: North Macedonia

Dispatcher of freight

AMO FREIGHT LLC [05/02/2022 - 30/11/2022]

City: Bitola

Country: North Macedonia

Dispatcher of freight

ATS LLC [01/12/2022 - 20/02/2023]

City: Prilep

Country: North Macedonia

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Graphic tehnician

SOU Taki Daskalo [01/09/1993 – 05/05/1998] **Address:** Bitola, 7000 Bitola (North Macedonia)

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Macedonian

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING C1 READING C1 WRITING C1

SPOKEN PRODUCTION C1 **SPOKEN INTERACTION** C1

DIGITAL SKILLS

Microsoft Office / Social Media / Google Drive / Zoom / Google Docs / Communicative Skills and great capability to organize works activities

DRIVING LICENCE

Driving Licence: B